Shopping Hours: [11am-8pm](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/hours/ "Shopping Hours:")

  |  

89˚F Sun

[Seminole Towne Center home page Seminole Towne Center logo SEMINOLE TOWNE CENTER](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/ "Click to return to the home page.")

[Seminole Towne Center home page Seminole Towne Center logo SEMINOLE TOWNE CENTER](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/ "Click to return to the home page.")

Hey there, VIP

You Have

### some new deals!

Click the link below to view deals from your favorite stores!

### Hey there, VIP Start Saving Now

Click below to follow your  
favorite stores and then  
watch the savings grow!

### Become a  
Seminole Towne Center VIP

Follow your favorite stores  
and be the first to know about  
sales, events, and more!

* |

* Search 

Search 

Discover

The Best Brands

seminoletownecenter.com Privacy Policy
======================================

This website, [seminoletownecenter.com](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/), is owned by Kohan Retail Investment Group and operated by Placewise LLC (Placewise).

We know that your privacy is important to you, and we work hard to earn and keep your trust. We have created this Policy to let you know what Personal Information we collect when you use this Site, how we use and share the Personal Information we collect,  how we protect your privacy, the choices available to you regarding our use of your information and how you can opt-out of having your information collected.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us using the following information:

### Seminole Towne Center

200 TOWNE CENTER CIR  
Sanford, FL 32771  

(An email address has been hidden from spam bots here. Enable javascript to see it.)

Table of Contents
-----------------

Effective Date
--------------

February 10, 2023

Your Consent
------------

Please take a few minutes to review this Policy before using this Site. The Site is intended for use by residents of the United States (“U.S.”) or non-residents that agree to use the Site in accordance with U.S. laws, our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you further represent and warrant that you (i) are located inside the U.S., or (ii) are located outside the European Union (“EU”) and agree to be bound by U.S. laws. You may not use the Site from the EU. Use of and access to the Site is void where prohibited. By using this Site you are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Policy, you may not access or use this Site.

This Policy is Part of our Terms of Use
---------------------------------------

This Policy is part of the [Terms of Use](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/terms/) that govern your use of this Site. A link to our [Terms of Use](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/terms/) is provided at the bottom of each page of this Site.

Privacy Notices
---------------

This Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by “privacy notices” posted on this Site. These Privacy Notices provide a level of detail that we cannot provide in this more general description of our privacy practices. For example, certain pages of this Site may contain Privacy Notices providing details about the Personal Information we collect on those pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information.

Types of Information We Collect
-------------------------------

_Information You Volunteer._ Kohan Retail Investment Group collects the Personal Information you and others knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use this Site. For example, we collect the Personal Information you submit when you register with this Site, participate in a contest, sign up for our newsletters, comment on a news item, or contact us with questions.

_Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser._ We collect information that is sent to us automatically by your Web browser. This information typically includes your IP address, the identity of your Internet service provider, the name and version of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. Generally, we do not link the information provided by your browser to your Personal Information.

_More About IP Addresses._ An “IP address” is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. It is used to identify your computer’s “location” in cyberspace, so that the information you request can be delivered to you.

IP addresses do not include your name, e-mail address, or other information that identifies you personally, but in some cases, they can be used to identify you. For example, if you have registered with this Site, we may link your IP address to account information that identifies you personally. We may also provide your IP address to our third-party service providers who can use it to identify your state and zip code. This gives us valuable demographic information about the individuals who use this Site. In addition, if, we suspect fraud or a threat to the security of this Site, we may share our server logs—which contain users’ IP addresses—with the appropriate investigative authorities, who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.

_Cookies and Similar Technologies._ We use “cookies” and other Web technologies (such as clear gifs, web beacons or similar devices) to collect information and support certain features of this Site. For example, we may use these technologies to:

* collect information about the ways visitors use this Site—which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page;
* to support the features and functionality of this Site—for example, to save you the trouble of re-entering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits; and
* to personalize your experience when you use this Site.

Generally, the information we collect using these Web technologies does not identify you personally. If, however, you have created a user identity, for example, by registering on this Site, we may link the information we collect using these Web technologies to other information that identifies you personally, use such third party information to enhance the information we collect using these web technologies, and/or provide access to or share the information we collect with third parties, including but not limited to data vendors, business partners, affiliates and clients.

Generally, if you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit this Site, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of this Site if your browser rejects our cookies.

_Information from your mobile device._ With your opt-in consent, we may collect location information from your mobile device and use that information to deliver tailored content through our mobile website or through our mobile applications. For example, if our mobile app recognizes that you are near a particular shopping center, we may send a message to your mobile device letting you know about a sale taking place at that shopping center. Assuming you have consented to our collection of location information from your mobile device, our mobile website and mobile app may collect such information even if you are not logged into them. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile tracking activities via their device settings. 

User-Generated Content
----------------------

The User-Generated Content you submit on or through this Site is available to others who visit this Site. In addition, we may repurpose User-Generated Content you submit on or through this Site for use in advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to User-Generated Content you submit on or through this Site. You should not submit any content you do not wish to make available to the general public, and you must take special care to make sure your submissions comply with our [Terms of Use](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/terms/). In particular, your submissions must not violate the privacy or other rights of others.

Third-Party Cookies
-------------------

In addition to the cookies Kohan Retail Investment Group delivers to your computer through this Site, certain third parties may deliver cookies to your computer for a variety of reasons and these third party services providers may collect non-personally identifiable information from our Site as well. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with this Site. [Learn more about Google Analytics](https://wikipedia.org/wiki/Google_Analytics).

We may ourselves, or other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors across nonaffiliated websites and delivering targeted advertisements either on this Site or on other websites. This form of advertising is based on anonymous information and not on any personally identifiable information. As a result, we and our vendor know your interests, but cannot personally identify you in connection with the delivery of that specific ad.

Kohan Retail Investment Group does not have access to, nor control over, the cookies of third-party service providers or advertisers. However, you have choices about the collection of information by third parties on this Site. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to this Site sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by [clicking here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en). Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to Kohan Retail Investment Group.  
  
We comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising set forth by the Digital Advertising Alliance. The online industry provides services through which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from certain data partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. If you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected during your visits to this or other sites, please [click here](http://optout.aboutads.info/) and/or [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). Please note that by opting out, you will continue to see generic advertising that is not tailored to your specific interests and activities. To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted out on your desktop browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device.

Please note that we do not respond to or honor “do not track” (a/k/a/ DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

Your access to this Site will not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

Facebook Log-in
---------------

You may choose to register, log-on, or enhance your profile on this Site with the Facebook Log-in feature. By doing this, you are asking Facebook to send us registration information from your Facebook profile. We treat that information as we do any other information you give to us when you register, log-on, or enhance your profile. After you have connected, Facebook also sends us additional information from your profile that allows us to display a Facebook module on the pages you view.

How We Use Personal Information Collected Through This Site
-----------------------------------------------------------

Generally, we use the Personal Information we collect through this Site

* to provide the information, products and services you request;
* to better understand your needs and interests;
* to provide you with a personalized experience when you use this Site;
* to provide you with effective customer service;
* to improve the content, functionality and usability of this Site;
* to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this Site;
* to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with any preferences you have expressed to us);
* to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us (in accordance with any preferences you have expressed to us);
* to improve our products and services;
* to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
* for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes; and
* for any other purpose identified in any other agreement between you and us.

Please note that if you specifically consent to additional uses of your Personal Information, we may use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with that consent. Please see below for information about the choices you have about the ways we use your Personal Information. We do not sell your PII to third parties or mass marketers.

Your Choices
------------

In General. We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information. Discussed above are choices you have about delivery of cookies to your computer through this Site. In addition, we generally will ask you to indicate your choices at the time we collect your Personal Information. For example, before we collect location information from your mobile device using our mobile website or our mobile app, we will ask for your affirmative consent to do so. In addition, your mobile device may allow you to adjust your settings so that location information is not available to any mobile website or mobile app. If you have questions about the security and privacy settings of your mobile device, please refer to instructions from your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device. In addition, if you register on this Site, we provide you with an opportunity to “opt out” of receiving certain communications from us and/or our business partners. We will also include an “unsubscribe” link in each electronic newsletter or promotional e-mail we send you, so that you can inform us that you do not wish to receive such communications from us in the future.

Previously Expressed Preferences. You may change previously expressed preferences regarding how we use your Personal Information. If you have registered with this Site or downloaded our mobile app, you may be able to change certain privacy preferences through your account settings. Otherwise, if at any time you wish to be taken off our mailing lists, please contact us using the [information provided above](#ContactInfomation). Please provide your full name, postal address, and e-mail address so that we can find you on our mailing lists. Once we have the information we need, we will remove you from our mailing lists as you have requested. Please give us a reasonable amount of time to honor your request.

How to Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information
----------------------------------------------------------

If you have registered with this Site or downloaded our mobile app, you may be able to access, update, or correct your Personal Information through your account settings. Otherwise, you may need our help. If you wish to access, update, or correct your Personal Information, please contact us using the [information provided above](#ContactInfomation). We will respond to you within a reasonable time and, in any case, within the time limits established by applicable law. We may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, we will provide access and correct or delete any inaccurate information you discover. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so or if we are unable to verify your identify.

Steps We Take to Safeguard your Personal Information
----------------------------------------------------

We maintain reasonable administrative, physical, and technological measures to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information you submit on or through this Site. Unfortunately, no website, server or database is completely secure or “hacker proof.” We therefore cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will not be disclosed, misused or lost by accident or by the unauthorized acts of others. We retain your Personal Information, if provided by you through the Site, for as long as your inquiry is active (as determined by us) and for a reasonable time thereafter, or if applicable, for as long as you remain on our marketing list. Even if we delete some or all of your Personal Information, we may continue to retain and use aggregate, anonymous data previously collected and/or anonymize and aggregate your personal information.

How We Share Your Personal Information With Others
--------------------------------------------------

Placewise. Placewise LLC powers this Site and manages the Personal Information we collect through this Site. As such, Placewise helps us with our promotional efforts and conducts surveys related both to this Site and your shopping experiences at Seminole Towne Center, among other activities. In addition, we allow Placewise to use your Personal Information for its own marketing purposes. In particular, Placewise operates the Placewise Network, which is a network of various shopping centers for which Placewise powers websites. Placewise may use the Personal Information you submit on or through this Site to contact you about other malls that we own.

Other Third–Party Vendors. We may share Personal Information collected through this Site with other third-party vendors who act for or on behalf of Kohan Retail Investment Group. These third-party vendors may need information about you to perform their functions. However, unlike Placewise, they are bound by law or contract to protect your Personal Information and are only allowed to use the Personal Information to perform services on our behalf.

Business Transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to successor organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation of this Site to another organization or if we merge with another organization. If such a transfer occurs, the successor organization’s use of your Personal Information will still be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

Compliance with Laws and Protection of Our Rights and the Rights of Others. We may disclose your Personal Information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order, or a subpoena. We may also disclose your Personal Information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of this Site; to enforce or apply our online [Terms of Use](https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/terms/) or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.

As Described in a Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as described in any Privacy Notice posted on the Web page where you provide that information. By providing your personal information on that Web page you will be consenting to the disclosure of your personal information as described in that Privacy Notice.

Children Under the Age of Thirteen
----------------------------------

We are proud of this Site and we strive to ensure that it does not offend people of any age. However, this Site is not intended for children or minors under the age of thirteen years without the permission of a parent or guardian. If you believe that a child has submitted Personal Information on or through this Site without the consent and supervision of a parent or guardian, please contact us using the [information provided above](#ContactInfomation).

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

This Site contains links to websites operated by other organizations, including websites operated by our third-party service providers and other third parties. This Policy does not apply to Personal Information collected on any of these third-party websites. When you access third-party websites through a link on this Site, please take a few minutes to review the privacy policy posted on that site.

This Policy May Change
----------------------

This Policy describes Kohan Retail Investment Group’s current policies and practices with regard to the Personal Information we collect through this Site.

We are continually improving and adding to the features and functionality of this Site and the services we offer through this Site. As a result of these changes (or changes in the law), we may need to update or revise this Policy. Accordingly, we reserve the right to update or modify this Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy behind the link marked “Privacy Policy” at the bottom of each page of this Site. Your continued use of this Site after we have posted the revised Policy constitutes your agreement to be bound by the revised Policy. However, we will honor the terms that were in effect when we gathered data from you.

For your convenience, whenever this Policy is changed, we will alert you by posting a notice on our home page for sixty days. We will also update the “effective date” at the top of this page. If more than sixty days goes by between your visits to this Site, be sure you check the effective date to see if this Policy has been revised since your last visit.

You may access the current version of this Policy at any time by clicking the link marked “Privacy Policy” at the bottom of each page of this Site.

Definitions
-----------

The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Kohan Retail Investment Group.

The term “Personal Information” refers to information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. Examples of Personal Information include your name, address, and e-mail address.

The term “Policy” refers to this online privacy policy.

References to this “Site” refer to the website owned by Kohan Retail Investment Group and located at https://www.seminoletownecenter.com/.

The term “User-Generated Content” refers to all of the text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, sounds, video, audio-video clips, and other content you post on or through this Site using the social networking tools we make available to registered members of this Site. One way that User-Generated Content differs from other information you provide to us is that, once submitted, User-Generated Content is made available instantaneously to others who visit this Site. Examples of User-Generated Content include comments posted to discussion boards and product reviews.

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of your information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy. You understand that data stored in the USA may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the USA.

Seminole Towne Center  

200 TOWNE CENTER CIR  
Sanford, FL 32771  

### Information

Visit Our Centers Other Kohan Centers Anderson Mall Animas Valley Mall Asheville Mall Birchwood Mall Brass Mill Center Chautauqua Mall Colonial Park Mall Cumberland Mall The Crossroads Mall Eastridge Mall Emerald Square Fashion Square Mall Fairlane Town Center Findlay Village Mall Gadsden Mall Greenwood Mall Holiday Village Mall Indiana Mall Indian River Mall Jasper Mall Lansing Mall Livingston Mall Lima Mall Lufkin Mall The Mall at Robinson Mall St. Vincent The Mall at Sierra Vista Marshalltown Mall McKinley Mall Montgomery Mall North Town Mall Northwoods Mall Pierre Bossier Mall River Hills Mall Rolling Oaks Mall Santa Fe Place Seminole Towne Center Sikes Senter Spring Hill Mall Temple Mall Town Center at Cobb Towne West Square Triangle Town Center Valle Vista Mall Valley View Vicksburg Mall Washington Crown Center Washington Park Mall Westwood Mall The Westwood Mall

© 2024 Kohan Retail Investment Group

Alert

Close

Sorry

Your login link has expired.  
To login please generate a new link.

SEND NEW LINKProcessing...

Close
